Now I'm going to give you all 1015 steps.
Yes!
That's right, Mr. Tohoku.
Please think of a word as you climb the stairs and announce it at the end!
Chocolate collaborative fandu
Good morning!
I'm very shy in the morning.
Good morning.
Stop it!
What? Really.
First, let's buy tickets.
Buy tickets?
Ticket?
Train tickets.
Where are we going?
I don't know.
I'm getting really nervous.
You know, in the middle of the rush hour...
You're right.
I'm really nervous.
Great. I want to go.
I'll be there.
I'm gonna go.
I'm going.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Ending
He's so cute.
What do you think it does?
I think it's very Kamotsurizuk-esque.
Now?
But I don't think
I don't think Mr. Northeast will do anything fun.
Fun things.
What? I said fun.
Okay, everybody, we're going down next.
I knew it. The mountain.
What the hell?
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait. Okay.
We're going down next.
What?
There's something in there.
Good morning.
You want some more?
Let's do it again.
Revenge.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
No, no, no, no.
Yay.
yay yay yay
I'm not on anything, but it's totally beautiful
I'll make an announcement before we leave.
Yes, ma'am.
You all said you were going to make costumes on YouTube
Yes, sir
And you asked me to come up with a four-letter word.
And now they're asking us to forget about it.
It is said that if you climb the temple, your troubles will disappear.
When you climb the 1015 steps, your troubles disappear.
Your mind will become empty and you will be able to think more easily.
From now on, I would like you all to climb the 1015 steps.
1015 steps.
Whoo!
Yay!
Yes!
We'll ask the audience to think of a word as they climb and announce it at the end.
Wait, we're leaving? Only here, but I'm the representative of Yamagata!
Ha-ha-ha!
That's right.
It's Yamagata.
I'm out first today.
It's work.
It's too much trouble to think about it, so let's just get up there.
Ha-ha-ha.
Why not?
Why?
There's quite a few of these out there.
Okay, let's go!
Uh-oh.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is it.
I really thought it was this way.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, I thought it was this way.
I'm going back.
Engine.
Shall we go?
Wow.
This is gonna be fun.
Let's go with the engine.
Let's jump and practice.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, everyone climb up one step at a time.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
Let's turn off the sound.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's go for it.
Yes, sir.
Let's do it.
Let's go!
Let's go for it.
Let's do it.
Yes, ma'am.
Galen.
Baka.
NINE.
Nino.
Kel
Ilano
Kuma
Mio
Golden Beast
Ignatura Tractor Ball
Yay!
I can't see you.
Hanwa
Yay go
W
nane
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH
Arcade
nya ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
nya
uh
I knew it!
what
zero
bejean
It's a flat road, but it's a slope...
I know, it's hard to go there because it's so scary.
I'm handcoco, guys.
Don't worry, I'm tired.
The air is so good!
It's soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo good!
It's minty and delicious.
It's sooooo good
Tougher than childbirth.
No, no, no, you haven't experienced that.
I'm glad it didn't rain.
I would have cried if it had rained
I would have cried.
I'd have given up.
The mountains, you know, the calm ones.
And the funny ones.
You know, the people who are watching...
Lying down
Eating sweets, drinking juice.
Watching.
I don't even have the energy to talk.
I don't have the energy to talk.
Here we go.
This way.
I'll be careful.
And...
Nine hundred and ninety.
I couldn't say.
Hmm.
CAPPI.
I can see the finish line.
What?
Yeah, it's Shagga.
580 to go.
You're so sweet.
Let's just keep going and keep going.
Are you okay? Are you okay, photographer?
You're being so nice.
The people watching are demons.
Demon!
We're almost there!
Just a little more.
Oh, he's doing it.
That's great.
Wow.
And...
Huh.
Is it still there?
Is there more?
Plenty.
Are you sure about that?
It's all right.
Is it already there?
Isn't that what you started out to do?
That's hard!
It's good training.
It's fun.
Cold is good.
Sweat is greatI'm sweating so hard.
Let's go for it.
Let's go
Oh, my God, it's beautiful.
Look at the view!
It's so beautiful!
Wow!
Miyu, one more time!
Are we done?
Is it over?
Yay!
It's over!
I'm sweating so hard.
Come here, you guys.
Come to my house.
Welcome to my house.
Delicious cake.
Yes!
100 points!
It happened.
We're home.
We made it home.
Yeah!
Bye!
And this sweat
La la la la la la la
The whole story of us.
In this 20-minute video
You can see it all in this 20-minute video.
Ha-ha-ha.
No cuts.
Let's fast-forward.
What?
Wait, wait, wait.
I thought I did a pretty good job.
No.
We're done.
I don't know...
I climbed it once when I was in seventh grade.
I don't remember it being this hard.
I feel my age.
I feel old.
Have you gotten rid of your troubles?
What are troubles?
I knew that in the first place.
Cute.
Hello, there.
She's got her back to you.
I like you.
I like it.
That's it.
Hey, Auntie.
That's great.
Such a
Beautiful.
Did I start?
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, please.
Do you want me to key it?
I'll take the insert, please.
Yes, I'll open it and I'll take it.
Yes, sir.
Yes, please.
Yui got it!
Thank you very much.
Cool.
So cool!
Yui means not only that this world belongs to you.
It also means that you are the only one in the world, so you have to live your life on your own.
So I chose "Yui ga Dokuson" because it has another meaning.
Cool. Thank you. Cool. Cool.
Let's go for it! Let's go for it!
I'll do my best.
Kousai demei!
What's that?
It means to be beautiful and take all the attention away from the people around you.
I want to be beautiful on the inside as well as in the background.
It's a little hard to go after this.
But I'm going!
Reflecting without eyes!
You just climbed up without thinking, didn't you?
We have a dream of Budokan.
We have to think about that dream... but we have to think about it.
But we don't think about it... that's right.
I understand.
I have to think about it a lot.
But I want to forget about it and go forward toward that destination.
I'm just going for it.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you for your hard work today!
No more glowing eyes!
What?
Wait, is that a four-letter word?
This is...This is...
What did you say?
"River man.
"Creamy"?
It means "cuteness knows no bounds.
Cute!
Now, if you come up here like this, you're still cute.
Everyone is saying that cuteness is unlimited.
Cute!
Next, we will be taught
Northeast line love!
So, with these words in my heart
I would like to express my wish that the 9 of us will do our best
I'll write it down!
Yay!
Congratulations!
I'm Shinji, the 9 star!
Shonen manga!
Seriously?
That's...
That was Hikaru's idea.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'll go next.
Causes and Effects
Tired?
A little.
It's like...
It's like, if you do good things.
Like, if you did good things in your past life.
If you do good things in your past life, good things will happen now.
So, if you all sit with your grandmother or something...
You'll win a ticket to the show.
That's nice.
If you say something nice...
I'll be there.
It's a book.
This is...
It's the theme of my life.
Leave it to others
Finally
In Yamagata
I, Shaun the Sheep, will be the last to go!
Straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw...
Alone?
Four straws, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw, straw...
What's the matter? Why did you decorate the bird with this?
I don't know, but we're all set.
That's good.
Great. It's like they all have their own style.
Hey, it's something...
It's good to be up here.
Yeah, it's nice.
That was good.
So, please keep watching YouTube!
Please watch it!
Subscribe to our channel while you still can.
Okay.
Oh, can I tell you something already?
Today.
Subscribe today.